(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
Attention: To all visitors
マスクの着用にご協力ください
マナーモードに設定してください
撮影/録音/録画は禁止
Please wear a mask / Use silent mode
No photography, recording, or filming
公演中に声を出しての応援はご遠慮ください
公演中は自席の前で立ってご観覧いただけます
公演中は席の移動をお控えください
No loud cheering / You may stand at your seat
Please refrain from moving seats
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish
OFFICIAL MERCHANDISE SHOWCASE
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
Attention: To all visitors
マスクの着用にご協力ください
マナーモードに設定してください
撮影/録音/録画は禁止
Please wear a mask / Use silent mode
No photography, recording, or filming
公演中に声を出しての応援はご遠慮ください
公演中は自席の前で立ってご観覧いただけます
公演中は席の移動をお控えください
No loud cheering / You may stand at your seat
Please refrain from moving seats
Weiss Schwarz Card Collection
こんにちは。
Hello.
ホロライブ 3rd fes. Link Your Wish...
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish...
誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
開演に先立ちまして、
Prior to the start of the performance,
ご来場のお客様にお願いがございます。
we have a request for the guests in attendance.
新型コロナウイルス感染拡大防止対策として、
As a measure to prevent the spread of the new coronavirus,
マスクの着用、手指の消毒、
we request your cooperation with wearing a mask, hand disinfection,
ソーシャルディスタンスのご協力をお願いしております。
and social distancing.
ご観覧いただく際や、ロビー内でも、
While viewing the show and even in the lobby,
お客様同士の距離間隔を保っていただくよう、ご協力をお願いいたします。
please cooperate by maintaining distance between each other.
飛沫防止のため、声出しなどの応援はお控えいただけますよう、お願いいたします。
To prevent droplets, please refrain from vocal cheering.
入場時に検温にて体調確認をさせていただいておりますが、
We checked your physical condition with a temperature check at entry,
万が一、体調に異変を感じた場合は、
but if you feel any change in your condition,
無理をせず、スタッフへお声がけください。
don't push yourself and please alert a staff member.
客席内での携帯電話、スマートフォンの利用は禁止です。
Use of mobile phones and smartphones in the seating area is prohibited.
スマートフォンは、新型コロナウイルス接触確認アプリ
Smartphones are used for the new coronavirus contact
「COCOA」を使用するため、電源はお切りにならず、
confirmation app "COCOA," so do not turn off the power.
開演までにマナーモードに設定し、おしまいください。
Please set it to silent mode before the show starts and put it away.
また、携帯電話、スマートフォンなどによる、
Filming, recording, and videotaping
撮影、録音、録画は、固くお断りいたします。
with mobile phones or smartphones is strictly prohibited.
万が一、発見した場合は、データを削除の上、
If discovered, we will delete the data
退場していただく場合がございます。
and you may be asked to leave.
客席内での、模造刀、サイリウム、ジャンプ等の危険行為、
Dangerous acts like using imitation swords, psylliums, or jumping,
ルールに反したコンサートライトの使用は、禁止となります。
and the use of unauthorized concert lights are prohibited.
以上のことがお守りいただけない場合は、
If the above rules are not followed,
公演を一時中断、もしくは中止させていただく可能性がございます。
the performance may be suspended or canceled.
また、本公演では、お席の前に立ち、
Also, for this performance, standing in front of your seat
ご観覧いただくことを許可しております。
to view the show is permitted.
このほか、本公演では、避難誘導等の点灯を行ないます。
Additionally, lights for evacuation guidance will be turned on.
万が一、避難が必要になった場合は、
In the unlikely event an evacuation is necessary,
すぐに誘導灯を点灯させますので、
emergency lights will be turned on immediately,
係員の指示に従って動いていただきますよう、お願いいたします。
so please follow the instructions of the staff.
公演終了後は、規制退場へのご協力のほど、よろしくお願いいたします。
After the performance, we ask for your cooperation with staggered exits.
スタッフの指示があるまで、ご自分のお席でお待ちください。
Please wait at your seat until instructed by the staff.
最後に、本公演は、映像配信、および
Finally, for this performance, video streaming
記録撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、
and recording cameras are in the venue,
お客様の様子が映り込む可能性がございます。
and guests may be filmed.
これらの映像や写真は、プロモーション等に使用される可能性がございますので、
These videos and photos may be used for promotions,
あらかじめご了承ください。
so please be aware of this in advance.
それでは、開演まで、しばらくお待ちください。
Now, please wait a moment until the show begins.
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
Attention: To all visitors
プレミアムブースター ホロライブプロダクション
Premium Booster: Hololive Production
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish DAY 1
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ
Weiß Schwarz
ホロライブプロダクションのブースターパックでも...
Even with the Hololive Production booster pack...
止まらない、ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Unstoppable, Weiß Schwarz!
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション 好評発売中！
Booster Pack Hololive Production is now on sale!
ブシロード
Bushiroad
アニメが大好きな中外鉱業コンテンツ部です！
We're the Chugai Mining Contents Division, and we love anime!
もっともっと！
More and more!
アニメを楽しみたい！
We want to enjoy anime!
そんな想いでアニメグッズを企画開発して、インターネットで販売しています！
With that in mind, we plan and develop anime goods and sell them online!
アニメとコラボしたカフェもやってます
We also run collaboration cafes!
最新情報はTwitterで！
Check our Twitter for the latest info!
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
SPECIAL LIMITED ITEMS
アクリルキーホルダー ¥1,700
Acrylic Keychain ¥1,700
アクリルジオラマ ¥3,500
Acrylic Diorama ¥3,500
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
Attention - To all visitors
Attention: To All Visitors
マスクの着用にご協力ください
Please cooperate by wearing a mask.
マナーモードに設定してください
Please set your phone to silent mode.
撮影/録音/録画は禁止とさせていただきます
Photography and recording are prohibited.
公演中に声を出しての応援はご遠慮ください
Please refrain from cheering out loud.
ライト・拍手で応援をお願いします
Support with penlights and applause.
席の移動はお控えください
Please refrain from moving from your seat.
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish DAY 1
公演ハッシュタグ #つながるホロライブDAY1
Concert Hashtag: #つながるホロライブDAY1
ペンライト / Tシャツ / マフラータオル
Penlight / T-shirt / Muffler Towel
公式ペンライトカラーまとめ
Official Penlight Color Summary
ウインドブレーカー / トートバッグ / サコッシュ
Windbreaker / Tote Bag / Sacoche
ロゴクッション / タペストリー / ラバーバンド
Logo Cushion / Tapestry / Rubber Band
コラボキャップ / サラサクリップ5本セット
Collaboration Cap / Sarasa Clip 5-Color Set
ランダム缶バッジ
Random Tin Badges
アクリルキーホルダー
Acrylic Keychains
クリアファイルセット / アクリルジオラマ
Clear File Set / Acrylic Diorama
トランプ 2022 / パンフレット
Playing Cards 2022 / Pamphlet
コーチジャケット / クルースウェット
Coach Jacket / Crew Sweatshirt
S/S Tシャツ / L/S Tシャツ
S/S T-shirt / L/S T-shirt
Attention ご来場の皆様へ (再掲)
Attention: To All Visitors (Reminder)
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ プレミアムブースター
Weiß Schwarz Premium Booster
アクリルカードスタンド / カードバインダー
Acrylic Card Stand / Card Binder
ミニフィギュア / アクリルスタンド
Mini Figures / Acrylic Stands
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
マスクの着用にご協力ください / 撮影・録音・録画は禁止
Attention: To all attendees
Please wear a mask / No filming or recording
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
声を出しての応援はご遠慮ください / ライト・拍手で応援を
Attention: To all attendees
Please refrain from shouting / Support with lights and clapping
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish DAY 1
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
マスクの着用にご協力ください / 撮影・録音・録画は禁止
Attention: To all attendees
Please wear a mask / No filming or recording
マスクの着用にご協力ください / COCOAを使用してください / 撮影・録音・録画は禁止
Please wear a mask / Use the COCOA app / Photography and recording are prohibited
公演中に声を出しての応援はご遠慮ください / 自席の前で立ってご鑑賞いただけます / 席の移動はお控えください
No shouting during the show / You may stand in front of your seat / No moving between seats
#つながるホロライブDAY1 / 開演までしばらくお待ちください
#ConnectingHololiveDAY1 / Please wait a moment until the show starts
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiß Schwarz!
ホロライブプロダクションのブースターパックでも、
Even with the hololive production booster packs,
止まらない、ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiß Schwarz is unstoppable!
ブースターパック
Booster Pack
ホロライブプロダクション
hololive production
好評発売中！
Now on sale!
ブシロード
Bushiroad
アニメが大好きな中外鉱業コンテンツ部です！
We're the Chugai Mining Contents Dept., and we love anime!
もっともっと！
More and more!
アニメを楽しみたい！
We want to enjoy anime!
そんな想いでアニメグッズを企画開発して
With that in mind, we plan and develop anime merchandise
インターネットで販売しています！
and sell them on the internet!
アニメとコラボしたカフェもやってます。
We also run collaboration cafes.
最新情報はTwitterで！
Check Twitter for the latest info!
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 SPECIAL LIMITED ITEMS
Attention: マスクの着用にご協力ください / COCOAを適用していただくため携帯電話の電源はオフにせず / 撮影・録音・録画は禁止とさせていただきます
Attention: Please wear a mask. / Keep phones on for the COCOA app. / Photography and recording are prohibited.
Attention: 公演中に声を出しての応援はご遠慮ください / 公演中は自席の前で立ってご鑑賞いただけます / 公演中は席の移動をお控えください
Attention: No shouting during the show. / Standing in front of your seat is allowed. / No moving from your seat.
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 プレミアムブースター ホロライブプロダクション
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022: Premium Booster hololive production
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish DAY 1
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish OFFICIAL ITEMS
PENLIGHT COLORS 公式ペンライトカラーまとめ
PENLIGHT COLORS: Official Penlight Color Guide
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
SPECIAL LIMITED ITEMS
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
Attention: To all attendees
マスクの着用にご協力ください / マナーモードに設定してください / 撮影・録音・録画は禁止
Please wear a mask / Please set your phone to silent mode / No filming, recording, or photography
公演中に声を出すのはご遠慮ください / 自席の前で立ってご鑑賞いただけます / 席の移動はお控えください
Please refrain from shouting during the show / You may stand in front of your own seat / Please do not move between seats
ホロライブ6期生のラプラス・ダークネスだ！
I am La+ Darknesss of hololive's 6th generation!
本日は、『hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish supported by Weiss Schwarz』DAY1にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to Day 1 of "hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish supported by Weiss Schwarz" today!
同じく…
And also...
ホロライブ6期生、秘密結社holoXの頭脳...
Hololive 6th gen, the brain of Secret Society holoX...
...博衣こよりだよ！
...is Hakui Koyori!
今日は僕たちが場内アナウンスを担当します。
Today, we will be in charge of the venue announcements.
今日一日、よろしくね。
Please look forward to it today.
ホロライブ6期生の鷹嶺ルイです。
I'm Takane Lui from Hololive 6th gen.
開演前にお客様にご案内がございます。
Before the show starts, I have some announcements for our guests.
まずはじめに、会場の皆様へのご案内です。
First, here are some announcements for those at the venue.
ロビー、客席内等ではマスクの着用が必須となります。
Wearing a mask is mandatory in the lobby and audience seats.
公演中の掛け声などは、新型コロナウイルス感染予防の観点から、ご遠慮ください。
Please refrain from shouting during the performance to prevent the spread of COVID-19.
ぜひ、拍手やペンライトなどでの応援をお願いいたします。
Instead, please support us with clapping and penlights.
また、会場内では立って応援いただいても問題ございませんが、
It's fine to stand while cheering in the venue,
周りのお客様のご迷惑にならないよう、ご配慮をお願いいたします。
but please be considerate of the guests around you.
続いて、配信をご覧の皆様へご案内です。
Next, here are some announcements for the live stream audience.
本ライブの録音、録画、ミラー配信や無断アップロードは固くお断りいたします。
Recording, filming, mirroring, or unauthorized uploads of this live performance are strictly prohibited.
その代わり、スクリーンショットでの撮影をしていただくことや、 SNSで感想を呟いていただくことは大歓迎なので、
However, screenshots and sharing your thoughts on social media are most welcome,
皆様、ハッシュタグ「#つながるホロライブDAY1」で 感想を呟いてSNSもいっぱい盛り上げてください。
so please use the hashtag #TsunagaruHololiveDay1 and liven up social media with your thoughts.
本ライブ配信ではデータ通信量が多くなることが想定されるため、 スマートフォンでご覧になる場合はWi-Fiのご利用を推奨いたします。
As this live stream involves high data usage, we recommend using Wi-Fi if you are watching on a smartphone.
インターネット回線の接続が不安定な場合は、 配信動画のクオリティを保証できませんので、ご了承ください。
Please note that we cannot guarantee the video quality if your internet connection is unstable.
また、最善の準備を行い、ライブ配信を実施いたしますが、 生配信である特性上、
We will do our best to prepare for the live broadcast, but due to its live nature,
不慮の障害で一時停止や映像の乱れなどが 起こる可能性があることを、あらかじめご了承ください。
please understand that unforeseen issues may cause pauses or video disruptions.
それでは、開演までもうしばらくお待ちください。
Now, please wait just a little longer for the show to start.
Hello everyone, this is IRyS from Hololive EN Project HOPE.
Thank you for coming to Hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish supported by Weiss Schwarz Day 1 today.
Similarly, I am Fauna from Hololive EN Council.
Today we will be in charge of all the announcements within the venue.
We hope you have an amazing time.
Likewise, I am Fauna from Hololive EN Council.
Before we start the show, we have some quick announcements.
We would first like to address the audience here today.
Masks are mandatory and must be worn in the lobby and audience seats.
Please refrain from shouting during the performances in order to prevent the spread of coronavirus.
We would love it if you supported us with your hands and penlights.
In addition, it is fine to stand up and cheer within the venue.
However, please be considerate of those around you when doing so.
Next is a short reminder to all of you who will be watching the live stream.
It is strictly prohibited to record, tape, mirror or illegally upload this live performance.
However, in return, you are definitely welcome to take screenshots and tweet about your experience on all social media platforms.
Please use the hashtag #TsunagaruHololiveDay1 and tweet your thoughts on social media.
This live performance is expected to require a large amount of data transmission and bandwidth.
We heavily recommend that you use Wi-Fi when viewing this event on your smartphones.
If your internet connection is unstable, we cannot guarantee the quality of the delivered video.
Although we will do our best to prepare for the live broadcasting, please keep in mind...
...that due to the nature of live broadcasts, there is a possibility of pauses or disruptions in the video due to unforeseen problems.
We would like you to please wait just a little longer for the show to start.
Halo semuanya! Namaku Ollie dari Hololive Indonesia generasi kedua.
Hello everyone! My name is Ollie from Hololive Indonesia second generation.
Terima kasih telah datang ke Hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish supported by Weiss Schwarz Day 1.
Thank you for coming to Hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish supported by Weiss Schwarz Day 1.
Dan aku Anya dari Hololive Indonesia generasi kedua.
And I'm Anya from Hololive Indonesia second generation.
Hari ini kami akan bertanggung jawab untuk membacakan pengumuman.
Today we will be in charge of reading the announcements.
Semoga hari ini akan jadi hari yang menyenangkan.
We hope today will be a fun day.
Halo semuanya! Namaku Reine dari Hololive Indonesia generasi kedua.
Hello everyone! My name is Reine from Hololive Indonesia second generation.
Pertama-tama, ada beberapa pengumuman untuk para tamu.
First of all, there are some announcements for the guests.
Kepada para tamu, kami mohon untuk selalu memakai masker saat berada di lobby maupun auditorium.
To the guests, we ask you to always wear a mask while in the lobby or auditorium.
...mohon tempat duduk.
...please stay in your seats.
Kami mohon juga untuk tidak mengeluarkan suara pada saat konser
We also ask you to refrain from making noise during the concert
untuk mencegah penyebaran virus korona.
to prevent the spread of the coronavirus.
Mohon dukung kami dengan tepukan tangan dan juga penlight ya!
Please support us with applause and penlights!
Selanjutnya adalah pengumuman untuk para pendatang yang menonton livestream.
Next is an announcement for viewers watching the livestream.
Anda dilarang untuk merekam, menayangkan,
You are prohibited from recording, broadcasting,
atau meng-upload ulang stream konser secara ilegal.
or re-uploading the concert stream illegally.
Tetapi sebagai gantinya, anda dianjurkan untuk upload screenshot
But in exchange, you are encouraged to upload screenshots
dan posting mengenai konser kami di media sosial!
and post about our concert on social media!
Mari gunakan tagar #つながるホロライブDAY1
Let's use the hashtag #つながるホロライブDAY1
di media sosial saat posting kesanmu mengenai acara ini.
on social media when posting your impressions of this event.
Karena konser live ini akan menggunakan data berukuran besar,
Because this live concert will use a large amount of data,
kami menyarankan penggunaan Wi-Fi jika anda menonton dari smartphone.
we recommend using Wi-Fi if you are watching from a smartphone.
Jika kualitas koneksi internet anda tidak memadai, kami tidak bisa menjamin kualitas video.
If your internet connection quality is inadequate, we cannot guarantee video quality.
Kami mohon pengertiannya.
We ask for your understanding.
Kami berkomitmen untuk mempersiapkan livestream ini dengan sebaik mungkin.
We are committed to preparing this livestream as well as possible.
Namun karena ini merupakan acara yang tayang secara langsung,
However, as this is a live broadcast,
tetap ada kemungkinan terjadinya masalah teknis. Kami mohon pengertiannya ya.
there is still the possibility of technical issues. We ask for your understanding.
本日は、ホロライブ3rdフェス、Link Your Wish...
Today is hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish...
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish
Supported by Weiss Schwarz
DAY1へご来場いただき、ありがとうございます。
Thank you for coming to DAY 1.
まもなく開演するよ！
The show is about to start!
みんな、準備はいい？
Everyone, are you ready?
せーの！
Ready, set...
DAY1 スタート！
DAY 1 START!
AZKi
さくらみこ
Sakura Miko
星街すいせい
Hoshimachi Suisei
赤井はあと
Akai Haato
白上フブキ
Shirakami Fubuki
夏色まつり
Natsuiro Matsuri
大空スバル
Oozora Subaru
戌神ころね
Inugami Korone
白銀ノエル
Shirogane Noel
宝鐘マリン
Houshou Marine
天音かなた
Amane Kanata
常闇トワ
Tokoyami Towa
姫森ルーナ
Himemori Luna
桃鈴ねね
Momosuzu Nene
尾丸ポルカ
Omaru Polka
一伊那尓栖
Ninomae Ina'nis
がうる・ぐら
Gawr Gura
ワトソン・アメリア
Watson Amelia
ムーナ・ホシノヴァ
Moona Hoshinova
同じ未来を見ていたい
I want to keep seeing the same future
あの夢手にしたい
I want to grab that dream
それぞれ違った　呼吸で
With each of our different breaths
走り出そう
Let's start running
どこ見ても真っ暗な場所に芽生えてさ
Sprouting in a place that's pitch black no matter where you look
ほんの小さな希望に　この瞳奪われた
My eyes were stolen by a tiny hope
不安で揺れる心を上手くチューニングして
Tuning my heart that's shaking with anxiety
ほんの小さな勇気を　振り絞っていたんだよ
I was squeezing out a tiny bit of courage
あきらめの文字　デリートして進む
Deleting the word "give up" and moving forward
苦しい時も　もう私は
Even during painful times, I am no longer
一人じゃないから
Alone anymore
だからもっと思い追いかけたい
So I want to chase my dreams even more
ワクワク止まらない
The excitement won't stop
想像を超えてく
Going beyond imagination
世界に見せてあげる
I'll show it to the world
アクセスしてみたい
I want to try to access it
後悔なんてさ　させない
I won't let you have any regrets
それぞれ違った　心で
With each of our different hearts
走り出そう
Let's start running
その空に輝く まぶしい思いは
The dazzling feelings shining in that sky
見たことのない光を リアルに届けるよ
Will deliver a light never seen before to reality
いつも聞こえるエールは ここにキャプチャーして
The cheers I always hear, I'll capture them here
また新しい光を 探したくなるよ
And I'll want to search for a new light again
君の笑顔は 保存して進む
I'll save your smile and move forward
悲しい時に 見返すよ
I'll look back at it when I'm sad
力が湧くから
Because it gives me strength
胸を張って 夢追いかけたい
I want to chase my dreams with pride
奇跡のストーリー 一緒に作ろう
Let's make a miracle story together
終わらない夢を
A never-ending dream
誰ひとり欠かせない 合わさったこの世界
No one is replaceable in this combined world
それぞれ違った心で 彩れば
If we color it with our different hearts
悲しい時も 寂しい時も
Even when sad, even when lonely
信じ合えるものがある
There is something we can believe in together
忘れずに この鼓動 鳴らし続けたい
Without forgetting, I want to keep this heartbeat sounding
終わらない世界に 溢れ出すよ
It will overflow into an endless world
笑顔たち
The smiles
憧れの舞台 立ちたい
I want to stand on the stage of my dreams
らしく輝きたい
I want to shine in my own way
時に涙して また笑い合いたい
Sometimes crying, I want to laugh together again
同じ未来も見たい
I want to see the same future too
あの夢 手にしたい
I want to grasp that dream
踏み出そう 奇跡の一歩を
Let's take a step forward into a miracle
意気切らして 夢追いかけたい
I want to chase my dreams even if I'm out of breath
ワクワク止まらない 想像を超えてく
The excitement won't stop, exceeding imagination
世界見せてあげる
I'll show you the world
アクセスしてみて 後悔なんてここにない
Try accessing it, there's no regret here
それぞれ違った心で 作ろうわ
Let's create it with our different hearts
白上フブキ SHIRAKAMI FUBUKI
Shirakami Fubuki
宝鐘マリン HOUSHOU MARINE
Houshou Marine
皆さんこんこんわー！白上フブキと！
Hello everyone! I'm Shirakami Fubuki!
皆さんこんこんわー！宝鐘マリンです！
Hello everyone! I'm Houshou Marine!
ついに私たちのデュエットですねー！
It's finally our duet!
皆さん最高に盛り上がっていきましょう！
Everyone, let's get hyped up to the max!
ワン・ツー・スリー、ヘイ、イェー！
One, two, three, hey, yeah!
ねぇそこのお嬢さん ここはもうスパダイス
Hey there, young lady, this is already Supardise
不満げな顔しちゃダメだよダメダメ
Don't look so grumpy, no no no
スマイルがパスポート それがあれば問題ない
A smile is your passport, if you have that, no problem
楽しんでいこうよ パラダイロ
Let's have fun, Paradiro
ハマっちゃった？
Are you hooked?
勇気出してワンツーステップ
Gather your courage and take a one-two step
今までの景色とは明らかに違う世界
A world clearly different from the scenery you've seen so far
フルブーストで楽しもうよ
With full boost, let's have fun
ワン・ツー・スリーでハピネスワールド
On one, two, three, Happiness World
今だけがチャンスだ 夢を掴もう
Now is our only chance, let's grab the dream
明日から上々フブキ
From tomorrow, everything's great Fubuki
想像もしたことない出来事が
Events you've never even imagined
きっと待ってるさ
Are surely waiting
新感覚なソングで心躍らせ
Make your heart dance with a fresh song
ポジティブにさあ面舵いっぱい
Stay positive and go hard-a-starboard
気持ち晴れ渡るその瞬間
The moment your feelings clear up
全速前進だ
Full speed ahead
いつだって一人じゃない 私たちと一緒に
You're never alone, together with us
最高にハッピーな人生を、ゲッツ！
Have the most happy life, get!
あーめでたい 眠い ずっとベッドでたくない
Ah, it's great but I'm sleepy. I don't want to get out of bed.
寝坊じゃない 今日は休みなんだ ついでにバイバイ
I'm not oversleeping, it's my day off! So, bye-bye.
そういうときはそう 何かやりたいことやってみよう
At times like that, let's try doing something you want to do.
消化してこう 君の内に秘める欲望
Let's unleash the desires hidden inside you.
甘い切り（甘い切り）
Sweet mist (Sweet mist)
声を出してシチュワーイェイ！
Raise your voice, sit-chu-wa-yay!
恥ずかしい気持ちとは 今すぐにバイバイさ
Say goodbye to feeling embarrassed right now.
エンジン全開 弾けようぜ
Full engine power, let's let loose!
1, 2, 3... Happiness World!
Happiness World
進め濃い my days 立ち止まらずに
Move forward in these intense days without stopping.
未来へのドア 叩けカンカン
Knock on the door to the future, knock-knock.
1秒も無駄にはできないよ
Can't afford to waste even a single second.
まだ曝け出せ
Show more of yourself.
いっそパンピー ハイテンションで
Just go with high tension like a normal person.
帆を上げろ お宝出航！
Raise the sails, treasures away!
後悔したくない その思いが
The feeling of not wanting any regrets...
追い風になる
...will become the wind at your back.
あまたな思い出して
Recall the countless memories.
私たちがいるから 最高にハッピーな運命を Yeah!
Since we're here, let's have the happiest destiny! Yeah!
皆さん！次は早口ですが
Everyone! The next part is fast-paced!
マリンちゃん噛まないでね！
Marine-chan, don't trip over your words!
船長は噛みませんよ！
I won't trip over them!
フブキちゃんこそ大丈夫ですか？
Are you sure you're okay, Fubuki-chan?
大丈夫！任せなさい！
I'm fine! Leave it to me!
年がら年中 一生 time
All year round, for a lifetime of showtime.
来るもの拒まず it's all right
Everyone's welcome, it's all right.
両手を上げましょう 万歳
Let's raise our hands, banzai!
まだまだこれでも物足りない
This still isn't enough!
古今東西の老若男女
Young and old, from all times and places.
楽しいことが一番でしょ
Having fun is what matters most, right?
少しだけ羽を外してみましょう
Let's let loose just a little bit.
ようこそワンダラ
Welcome to Wonderland.
今日も一歩一歩踏み出せばきっと
Take it step by step today, and surely...
人生の経験値ゲット
...you'll gain life experience.
ふとした何気ないことだって
Even the small, trivial things...
多分笑えるさ
...can probably make you laugh.
今だ！今だけがチャンスだ
Now! This is the only chance.
夢を掴もう
Let's grab our dreams.
明日から紙吹雪シルバー
From tomorrow, silver confetti.
想像したことない出来事がきっと待ってるさ
Unimaginable events are surely waiting for you.
待ってるさ
They're waiting.
シングアソングで心躍らせ
Sing a song and make your heart dance.
ポジティブにさあ面舵いっぱい
Stay positive, now hard to starboard!
気持ち晴れ渡るその瞬間
The moment your feelings clear up...
全速前進！
...full speed ahead!
無駄じゃない 私たちと一緒に
It's not in vain, together with us.
最高にハッピーな人生を Yeah!
Let's live the happiest life! Yeah!
せーの！みんなでハッピーな人生を Yeah!
One, two! Everyone, let's live a happy life! Yeah!
はい！ということで！改めてまして皆さん！
Yes! And so, once again, hello everyone!
こんしょー！マリンです！
Ahoy! I'm Marine!
えっ
Eh?
君たち！こんこんきつね！白上フブキでしょう！
Everyone! Kon-kon kitsune! It's Shirakami Fubuki!
サイリウム消して！サイリウム消して！
Turn off your lightsticks! Turn them off!
やばいやばいやばい！見知らぬ見知らぬ！
Oh no, oh no! We're strangers now!
マリン！暗い！
Marine! It's dark!
白上暗い！
Shirakami, it's dark!
遅いんだよ馬鹿野郎！
You're too slow, you idiots!
はいはいはいはい！皆さんサイリウム点けてください！
Okay, okay! Everyone, please turn your lightsticks back on!
はい点けてください！
Yes, please turn them on!
ということで改めてまして、白上フブキと宝鐘マリンです！
Once again, we are Shirakami Fubuki and Houshou Marine!
マリフブ！
Mari-Fubu!
何そのポーズ！
What's with that pose?
ちょっと対にしてみた対に！
I tried to make it symmetrical!
ちょっとね、やっぱバランスを見て。向きみたいな。
Well, I was looking at the balance. Like our orientation.
臨機応変！キュートなポーズ！いや可愛くない？
Adaptable! A cute pose! Isn't it cute?
二人でHappiness Worldをお届けしました！
The two of us performed 'Happiness World'!
いやーなんかこの曲うちの知ってますよね？
Man, you guys know this song, right?
いや知ってますよね、知らない人なんていないですよね？潜りだぞ知らない人って！
You know it, right? Everyone knows it! If you don't, you're a fake fan!
この曲ラジオで発表されて、我々もずっとラジオやってますからね。絆よ絆！
This song was announced on our radio show. We've been doing it for so long. It's our bond!
そう、道理道理！
Exactly, exactly!
ねー、ビジネスフレンドじゃない？
Hey, we're not just business friends, are we?
うん、もちろん！
Of course not!
えっ、本当に？ちょっと間が空いちゃった。まずい！
Wait, really? There was a bit of a pause there. Oh no!
やめてくださいもうちょっと！
Stop it already!
まぁでもね、フブちゃん！ついに！ホロフェス！始まりました！
But anyway, Fubu-chan! Finally! Holofes has begun!
1日目！うー！拍手拍手！
Day 1! Woo! Round of applause!
イェーイ！ありがとうございます！
Yay! Thank you very much!
いやー本当にね。色々練習してきたけどさ、ダンスどうだった？
Seriously. We practiced so much. How was the dancing?
いやさっきHappiness Worldさ、白上若干...
During 'Happiness World' just now, Shirakami was a little...
ちょっとね、あの、怪しいところあったんだけど
I had some shaky moments there...
マリンちゃんの方全然見れてなくて
I wasn't able to look at Marine-chan at all.
船長も実はフブちゃんの事全然見れてなかったんだけど
Actually, the Captain wasn't able to look at Fubu-chan at all either.
船長は、なんか、最後の最後のラスサビになって急に
At the very last chorus, the Captain suddenly...
「あれ、何だっけ？」ってなって
...was like, "Wait, what was next?"
なんか「あれ、ちょっと待って、あれ、あれ、あれ...」
Like, "Wait, hold on, uh, uh, uh..."
「あれ、こうだった。あれ、次なんだっけ？」みたいな
"Oh, it was this. Wait, what's next?" something like that.
焦りが出て、ちょっと、あわあわしました
I started panicking and got a bit flustered.
おー、いや、でも、可愛かったですもんねー
Oh, well, you were cute, so it's fine!
ねー
Yeah!
まあ、なんかね、そのちょっと遅れちゃったりね
Well, even the parts where you were a bit late,
できてないところまで、可愛い！
or couldn't quite do it, were cute!
優勝優勝！それは可愛くにょい！
Victory, victory! That's "cute-nyoi"!
お前...なんか...
You're... what...
ライブだぞ！やめるんだ！
We're live! Stop it!
さて、フブちゃん。3rd fesはね
Now then, Fubu-chan. For 3rd fes,
なんと言っても、やっぱり4期生や
above all else, there's the 4th gen,
5期生、
5th gen,
それに、ENやIDのみんな
and everyone from EN and ID.
そう！がついにね
Right! They're finally...
ついについによ！
Finally, finally here!
同じ、同じステージに！わー！
On the same, the same stage! Wow!
これは超楽しみですよねー
We're really looking forward to this!
いやー、もう本当にもう、そわそわドキドキで
Yeah, seriously, I'm all fidgety and excited.
この後もね、我々、ソロ曲もありますしね
And after this, we both have our solo songs too.
そうだよ！私、なんかちょっともう出番終わったみたいな空気なっちゃったけど
That's right! I feel like my turn is already over or something.
まだソロ曲ありますからね！
We still have our solo songs!
始まったばっかですからね、本当に
It's really only just begun.
どんなユニットが来るかとかもね
Also, which units will be coming up next...
そうそうそう、ぜひね
Right, right, please...
ちょっとぜひ予想して、ま、でも我々がもうここで終わっちゃったんで
...try to guess. Well, since we've finished our part here,
終わっちゃったんだよね、もう来ないことが
we've finished, so it's known we won't be back.
わかっちゃったけど...
We know that now, but...
え、もうこれっきりってこと？
Wait, you mean this is it?
そういうこと
That's right.
どういうこと？マリンちゃん...
What do you mean? Marine-chan...
やっぱビジネスフレンドだったの？白上とは
Was it just a "business friend" relationship with Shirakami after all?
そんなわけないじゃんかー
There's no way that's true!
あーノリが、いや、ちょっとライブでテンション上がって変なノリになってるぞ
Ah, the mood... no, my energy is up because of the live show and I'm being weird.
変なノリになってるよー
You're definitely being weird.
いやもうね、でもこの後も本当にいろんなね、メンバーが歌いますので
Well, anyway, after this, many different members will be singing.
まだまだここで力尽きちゃダメですからね、みなさん！
So you can't run out of energy here, everyone!
そうそう、こんな広い会場でちょっともう何でもできる
Right, in such a large venue, you can do anything.
そう、めちゃめちゃ広いでしょ？
Yes, it's incredibly large, isn't it?
ちょっと動き回る
Gonna move around a bit.
待って待って、白上！待って、来ないで、あー来ないで、やめて
Wait, wait, Shirakami! Wait, don't come over, ah, don't come over, stop it.
待て待て、足腰を...よし、倍返し！
Wait, wait, my legs... alright, double the payback!
めっちゃ疲れとるやんけー、ハァハァ...
I'm totally exhausted... *panting*...
やばい、やばい、すごい広い
Oh no, oh no, it's so wide.
ライブ会場でちょっと暴れ散らかしてもろて
Going a bit wild in the concert venue.
ちょっと、あっちこっち、
Wait, over here and there...
あっちこっち、アピールアピール！
Over here and there, appeal, appeal!
アピールしていこう、イエーイ！イエーイ！決めたー！
Let's appeal to them, yay! Yay! We did it!
見えとるかー、見えとるぞー
Can you see us? We can see you!
元気？元気？大丈夫ですか？
How are you? You good? Are you okay?
おばあちゃんですか？
Are you an old lady?
ちょっと疲れちゃったね、ちょっとね
I got a little tired, just a little.
ちょっと暴れ散らかさないでいただいて
Please stop going wild for a moment.
大丈夫？大丈夫、大丈夫
You okay? You're fine, you're fine.
この後、ソロ曲もあるって言ってるでしょ
I told you there are solo songs after this.
あ、そう、そう、ソロ曲もあるからね、みんなね。ちょっとね
Oh, right, right, there are solo songs too, everyone. Just a moment.
ねー。そう、一体何を歌うんでしょうかねー、ソロ曲ねー
Yeah. So, I wonder what we'll be singing for our solo songs?
え、でもやっぱ船長、フブちゃんは、ちょっとぶっちゃけ「あれ」かなーって思ってるんだけど
Well, but for the Captain, honestly, I'm thinking Fubu-chan will do "that".
「あれ」って何なの？
What do you mean by "that"?
「あれ」って何かなー？でもマリンちゃんは「あれ」かな？
I wonder what "that" is? But maybe Marine-chan will do "that"?
いや、ちょっと待って、その「あれ」じゃないかも、
Wait, hold on, it might not be that "that"...
あの、でもなんか、リハの時とか、なんか「あれ？」
But, like, during the rehearsal, it was like "Huh?"
あー、あー
Ah, ah.
ちょっとね、君たちは「あれ」だと思っているんだろうなあ
Well, I bet you all think it's "that".
「あれ」だろうと、「あれ」だろうと思っているんだろうなあ
You're thinking "that", or maybe "that".
本当かなー？
I wonder if that's true?
ちょっと気まずすぎる。でも「あれ」じゃないんだ、気まずいな
This is getting too awkward. But it's not "that", how awkward.
白上はね、みんなの予想してる「あれ」だと思うので
For Shirakami, I think it'll be "that" which everyone is predicting.
ぜひね、いっぱいサイリウム振ってくださいね！
So please, wave your glow sticks a lot!
ちょ、なんかまるで、わー、船長も「あれ」です。船長も「あれ」で
Wait, it's almost like... wow, the Captain is also "that". The Captain is also "that".
「あれ」って何？負けられ、
What is "that"? I can't lose...
いや、でも他のメンバーの曲もね、まだ、だって今、2曲目ですよ、まだ
No, but the other members' songs too... I mean, it's only the second song so far.
まだ、まだ2曲目ですからね！
It's still only the second song!
ていうかさ、よく考えたらさ、SSSをさ、
Come to think of it, we already did SSS,
早速、消化しちゃったけど、どうすんの、この先？
so what are we going to do for the rest of the show?
確かに、この後の全体曲？
True, the group songs after this?
そうよ。あー、どうしよう、わからない
Exactly. Ah, what should we do? I don't know.
わからない、あ、あ、あ...
I don't know, uh, uh, uh...
あー！ということで、そろそろお時間ですので、次の曲、次の曲行ってみましょう！
Ah! So, it's about time, let's move on to the next song, the next song!
行きましょうか！はい、皆さんね、どんどん盛り上がっていってくださいね！
Shall we go? Yes, everyone, keep getting more and more excited!
いってらっしゃーい！
Here we go!
せーの！
One, two...
つながる！ホロライブ！
Link! Hololive!
バッ！ちょっと白上！白上！白上！あー！
Pow! Wait, Shirakami! Shirakami! Shirakami! Ah!
天音かなた (AMANE KANATA)
尾丸ポルカ (OMARU POLKA)
戌神ころね (INUGAMI KORONE)
Nanubish-oryappash!
つかみも最高　本気（マジ）開始
A perfect start, getting serious now
三者三様　究極パキ
Three people, three ways, ultimate "paki"
天使の旋律　イッツ・マイ・くるくる
An angel's melody, it's my "kuru-kuru"
テキトーに頑張ろうぜ
Let's just do our best casually
そんなんだったええけどさ
That's fine and all, but...
必死に頑張ろうぜ
Let's work hard desperately
それが僕ら仕様だ
That's just how we are
ダサすぎちゃ面目丸損
It's embarrassing if we're too uncool
ビンボーっちゃ面目丸損
It's embarrassing if we're poor
パンチがバッチリ
Punches are perfect
キマって何決まってる
Looking good, what's decided?
幽体なんだっけ？ ドドンパ
Ghosts or something? Dodonpa
全心全霊 ちゃんと歓迎して
Welcome me with all your heart and soul
どこまでいっか 想像ちゃんと共感して
Empathize with the imagination of how far we'll go
ワープしよう 僕が言わんだもん 本当にするんだもん
Let's warp! I said I would, and I'm really doing it
現実超えろ未来 あぁ
The future that surpasses reality, ah
弱点も兵器 七転八倒
Weaknesses are weapons too, ups and downs
千万馬力 独走状態 ワンダランだって
Ten million horsepower, in the lead, even in Wonderland
楽しもう
Let's have fun
面白がれること探し 魂オーバー
Searching for fun things, soul overflow
返事聞かせてくれ
Let me hear your answer
右左なんかじゃない 決めて抜けて一直線
It's not about left or right, decide and break through
つまみたくならんなら発射 ライダー ワクワクしてさ
If you don't want to pick it, launch! Rider, getting excited
みんな！ 歓声上げていくぞ！ せーの！
Everyone! Raise your voices! One, two!
ご機嫌はあそばせのでさぁ！ 合致の出るまで回すぞ！
Make yourself at home! I'll keep spinning until we're in sync!
絶好です 散弾よ そんなこと言っちゃだめ おバカ
It's perfect, a scattershot! You shouldn't say such things, dummy
バランス後光 ありがとう 響き越えそう 全部おまけ
Balanced halo, thank you! Echoing through, all just a bonus
虎視眈々でいたいもんだって 意気ガンガンがいいもんだぜ
I want to be vigilant, and being high-spirited is great
方位に感ずり アンテナ張っていなくちゃ
Must sense the direction and keep my antenna up
いつでも心はちゃんと純粋で
My heart is always truly pure
いたいな 好奇心は絶えず熱心で
I want to stay that way, with curiosity always eager
うるさいって言い越せるんだ
I can shout over the noise
調子に乗ったらすぐ飽きられちゃうから あぁ
If I get cocky, people will get bored quickly, ah
最高ならもっと高い場所へ
If it's the best, then to even higher places
千万馬力 独走状態 ワンダランだって
Ten million horsepower, in the lead, even in Wonderland
しっかりとつけ 努力とは最後まで諦めないこと
Remember well, effort means not giving up until the end
メモっておいて
Take a note of that
本当はベイビー 自信なんかないよ
To be honest, baby, I have no confidence
本当はベイビー 不安ばかりで
To be honest, baby, I'm full of anxiety
泣きそうだって でもねベイビー
and feel like crying. But you know, baby...
挫けないって決めたの だからベイビー
I've decided not to give up. So baby,
挑戦したいの 未開の天 地無限のビートで 行くぜ！
I want to challenge the unexplored world with an infinite beat! Let's go!
全心全霊 ちゃんと歓迎して
Welcome me with all your heart and soul
どこまでいっか 想像ちゃんと共感して
Empathize with the imagination of how far we'll go
ワープしよう 僕が言わんだもん 本当にするんだもん
Let's warp! I said I would, and I'm really doing it
現実超えろ未来 あぁ
The future that surpasses reality, ah
弱点も兵器 七転八倒
Weaknesses are weapons too, ups and downs
千万馬力 独走状態 ワンダランだって
Ten million horsepower, in the lead, even in Wonderland
楽しもう
Let's have fun
面白がれること探し放題だぜ
There's no limit to searching for fun things
無限のフィールドへ
To the infinite field
ハプニングしちゃってもいい 止まらぬ一直線
It's okay if happenings occur, an unstoppable straight line
つまりこれが僕の航海なんだ 胸を張れ
In short, this is my voyage. Stand tall
今を生きるその意味を 明くる日もあくるくる日も
The meaning of living in the now, day after day
確かに進め まだ！
Steadily move forward, not yet done!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
Welcome! あなたは選ばれしポルカサーカス in 幕張のお客さま！
Welcome! You are the chosen Polka Circus guests in Makuhari!
やあやあお待たせしました！ とってもハッピーなアイドル、
Hey there, sorry to keep you waiting! A very happy idol,
愉快でかわいいアイドル、そして今は...
a fun and cute idol, and now...
ポルカサーカス！ ぜんぶ何が見たい？
Polka Circus! What do you want to see?
どんなことでもしてあげる！ 私は座長、その名も
I'll do anything for you! I'm the ringmaster, name of
尾丸ポルカ！ 絶対笑顔にさせちゃうぜ、スマイル！
Omaru Polka! I'll definitely make you smile, smile!
それじゃあ最後までライブ楽しんでいこうぜ！
Now then, let's enjoy the live until the very end!
準備はできてるか？ Are you ready?
Are you ready? Are you ready?
さあさあ近くにおいで きっと誰もが仰天
Come, come, step closer, I'm sure everyone will be amazed
奇想天外なショーの始まりさ！
It's the start of an extraordinary show!
じっと惹かれるでしょう ほら恐れずにね
You'll be drawn in, right? Look, don't be afraid
それでは準備OKですか？
Now then, are you ready?
愉快な動物たち 玉乗りピエロ
Cheerful animals, ball-balancing clowns
ハラハラドキドキしちゃうでしょう
It'll make your heart race, won't it?
魔縄くぐらせ 輪渡りして
Passing through the magic rope, jumping through hoops
ちょっとぐらいのドジなんて ご愛嬌よ！
A little clumsy mistake is just a charming touch!
Come on, light up! 喝采起きろライブ
Come on, light up! Let the cheers ring out, live
見逃さないで もっと騒いで もっとお手を叩け
Don't look away, make more noise, clap your hands more
ほら 本気出して置いて
Come on, show me your true strength
...でも回るようなサーカス
...even this rotating circus...
きっとここだけだよ
...I'm sure is only found here.
ホログラムみたい
Like a hologram,
キラキラ 奇跡が踊る
the sparkling miracles dance.
いつかは世界中を
Someday, I'll take
とりこにしちゃうぞ
the whole world by storm!
おっ、明日の演目はどうしようかな
Oh, what should tomorrow's program be?
屋根裏で秘密の作戦会議さ
A secret strategy meeting in the attic.
いっぱいの観客席があっと驚くような
To make the full audience gasp in surprise,
とびきりのショーを見せましょう
let's put on an extraordinary show!
思いついたらじっとしてられない
Once I have an idea, I can't stay still.
さぁ手引いて レッツゴー
Come on, take my hand, let's go!
あれがやりたい これがやりたい
I want to do this, I want to do that!
どうして時間足りないのー？
Why isn't there enough time?!
行くぜー！
Here we go!
みんな何色が好き？
What color do you all like?
ポルカはもちろんレッド、赤！
Polka's is, of course, red!
一緒に届けてね！
Send it along with me!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
みんなの好きな色もたくさん教えて！
Tell me lots of your favorite colors too!
その手を強く伸ばして！
Reach out those hands!
うまくいかなくて
When things don't go well,
空回ってばかりで
and I'm just spinning my wheels,
少し落ち込んじゃう日もあるけれど
there are days when I feel a bit down, but...
見ててね！
Keep watching!
大丈夫、いつまでも
It's okay, I won't stay
くよくよしてらんないし
gloomy forever.
顔を上げて 今日のステージがほら
Look up, because today's stage, look!
ねぇ 待ってるのさ
Hey, it's waiting for us!
さぁ 盛り上がってまいりました！
Now, we're really getting fired up!
ポルカおるか？
Is Polka here?
ポルカ歌うか！
Is Polka gonna sing?!
みんな手拍子してください！
Everyone, please clap your hands!
ポルカおるか？ ポルカ踊るか？
Is Polka here? Will Polka dance?
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
強く強く願うんだ どんな夢だって
Make a strong, strong wish, no matter what dream it is,
きっときっと叶うはず
it's sure to come true.
何も怖くない みんなの声は
Nothing's scary, because everyone's voices...
全部ちゃんと届いてるよ！
...are all reaching me clearly!
さぁ 新しい次元 新しい舞台へ
Now, to a new dimension, a new stage!
もっともっと突き進もう
Let's push further and further forward!
まだまだついておいで
Keep on following me!
笑い転げちゃう サーカス絶対ここだけだよ
This hilarious circus is definitely only here!
始めての仲間 景色に
With new friends and new scenery,
心も躍る
my heart is dancing too.
今にも世界中を
Even now, I'll take
とりこにしちゃうから
the whole world by storm,
目を離しちゃダメだぞ！
so don't take your eyes off me!
ヤッホー！
Yahoo!
今日はみんなの指を貰いに来たよー！
I've come to take everyone's fingers today!
あ、強制ではないからね
Ah, it's not mandatory, though.
ころねが歌い終わるまでにきれいに指を切り落としておいてください！
Please have your fingers neatly chopped off by the time Korone finishes singing!
行くぞー！
Here we go!
気がついたら同じ面ばかりプレイして
Before I knew it, I was playing the same stage over and over,
そしていつも同じ場所で死ぬ
and I always die in the same spot.
諦めずに消える足場に挑戦するけど
I don't give up and challenge the disappearing blocks, but
すぐに下に落ちるよ
I fall down immediately.
アイテム２号があれば楽に 向こうの岸まで着くけど
If I had Item 2, I could easily reach the other side, but...
何回やっても何回やってもエアーマンが倒せないよ
No matter how many times I try, I can't defeat Airman.
あの竜巻何回やっても避けられない
No matter how many times I try, I can't dodge those tornadoes.
後ろに回って撃ち続けても いずれは風に飛ばされる
Even if I get behind him and keep firing, I eventually get blown away by the wind.
タイム連打も試してみたけど 竜巻相手じゃ意味がない
I tried rapid-firing the pause button, but it's useless against the tornadoes.
だから次は絶対勝つために 僕はＥ缶だけは最後まで取っておく
So to make sure I win next time, I'll save my E-Tanks until the very end.
気がついたらライフもう少ししかない
Before I knew it, I barely have any lives left.
そしていつもそこで胃管だけ使う
And as always, I end up using only my stomach tube right there.
USE ITEM
諦めずにエイアムまでたどり着くけれど
I make it all the way to A-M without giving up, but...
すぐに残機なくなる
I lose my lives in no time.
GAME OVER
イフシールドがあれば楽にエイアムは倒せるけど
If only I had the Leaf Shield, I could beat A-M easily, but...
何回やっても 何回やっても
No matter how many times I try, no matter how many times I try,
ウッドマンが倒せないよ
I can't defeat Woodman!
落ちるこの葉は何回やっても避けれない
I can't dodge those falling leaves, no matter how many times I try.
後ろに下がって距離をとってもいずれは距離を詰められる
Even if I back away to keep my distance, he eventually closes in on me.
タイムレンヤも試してみたけどあいつのジャンプは潜れない
I tried using Time Stopper, but I can't slip under his jumps.
だから次は絶対勝つために僕は胃管だけは最後まで取っておく
So next time, to make sure I win, I'll save my stomach tube until the very end!
アイテム２号があれば楽に向こうの岸まで行けるけど
If I had Item 2, I could easily get to the other side, but...
何回やっても 何回やっても
No matter how many times I try, no matter how many times I try,
エイアムが倒せないよ
I can't defeat A-M!
あの竜巻は何回やっても避けれない
I can't dodge those tornadoes, no matter how many times I try.
後ろに回って撃ち続けてもいずれは風に飛ばされる
Even if I get behind him and keep shooting, I eventually get blown away by the wind.
タイムレンヤも試してみたけど竜巻相手じゃ意味がない
I tried using Time Stopper, but it's useless against tornadoes.
だから次は絶対勝つために僕は胃管だけは最後まで取っておく
So next time, to make sure I win, I'll save my stomach tube until the very end!
倒せないよ
I can't beat him...
みんな！いっぱいっぱい指ありがとう！
Everyone! Thank you for all the fingers!
こんなに指がもらえるなんて、ほんと幸せです！
I'm so happy to receive this many fingers!
みんなが痛みに耐えて切り落としてくれた指、大事にするからねー！
I'll treasure the fingers you all endured the pain to cut off for me!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
夏色まつり
Natsuiro Matsuri
大空スバル
Oozora Subaru
桃鈴ねね
Momosuzu Nene
Moonlight Merry-go-round, Candy-Go-Round, Ready-go-round
夢のようなスピードでエスコート
Escorting you at a dream-like speed.
時の流れはいつでもゆっくり
Time always flows slowly.
だけどハートの動くスピード
But the speed at which the heart moves,
気まぐれは
is so fickle.
聞かせてよ この場所へ
Let me hear you, so it reaches
ちゃんと届くように
this place clearly.
君の Clap Clap Clap
Your clap, clap, clap,
Everybody clap hands up!
Everybody, clap your hands!
Good story
Moonlight Merry-go-round, Candy-Go-Round, Ready-go-round, 夢のようなスピードで飛び立とう
Moonlight Merry-go-round, Candy-Go-Round, Ready-go-round, Let's take off at a dream-like speed!
歌に乗り込めばいけるんだ
If we jump into the song, we can make it.
ハイスピリズム止められない
This high-speed rhythm is unstoppable!
さあ Moonlight Merry-go-round, Candy-Go-Round, パラレルは始まりのベルが鳴り響く夜に
Now, Moonlight Merry-go-round, Candy-Go-Round, on this night where the bell of the parallel world rings out...
迎えに行くから
...I'm coming to pick you up!
同じビートで一つのナンバー奏でよう
Let's play one song with the same beat.
奏でよう
Let's play it!
ハートを1ミリでも動かせば
If you move your heart even just a millimeter,
奇跡起こす大きな一歩に繋がるから
it'll lead to a big step that creates a miracle.
つまらない時はワクワクを
When things are boring,
リリックスして
turn your excitement into lyrics.
つまらない時はワクワクを
When things are boring,
リリックスして
turn your excitement into lyrics.
...見よう
...let's see.
君とダンス ダンス ダンス
Dance dance dance with you.
Every party Shall we dance?
ステップ踏ねパーティーしよう
Let's step and party.
Sunlight Merri-Go-Round
Candy-Go-Round
Wonder land どっか行きたい場所へ
Wonder land, to somewhere you want to go.
連れていくよ
I'll take you there.
瞳閉じたら合図なんだ
Closing your eyes is the signal.
もうタイムスリップも止められない
Can't stop the time slip anymore.
Sunlight Merri-Go-Round
Candy-Go-Round
Colorful night どんな距離だって
Colorful night, no matter what the distance.
超えて会いに行く
I'll cross it to see you.
夜空を見上げて
Looking up at the night sky.
ドラマチックでもう忘れられない
So dramatic, I'll never forget it.
今にしよ
Let's do it now.
起きても醒めない魔法かけるから
I'll cast a spell that won't break even when you wake up.
始めようステージを
Let's start the stage.
君の胸のドキドキ
The pounding in your chest.
嘘じゃないよ
It's not a lie.
リアルだよ
It's real.
星も嬉しくて飛び回ってるよ
Even the stars are flying around with joy.
リズムを合わせるように
As if matching the rhythm.
とびきりな夢を
An extraordinary dream.
君と君と君と一緒に
With you, with you, together with you.
Moonlight Merri-Go-Round
Candy-Go-Round
Merry-Go-Round
夢のようなスピードで
At a dream-like speed.
飛び立とう 歌に乗り込めば行けるんだ
Let's take off, we can go if we ride the song.
タイムスリップも止められない
Can't stop the time slip.
Sunlight Merri-Go-Round
Candy-Go-Round
パレードは始まりの
The parade is the beginning.
ベルが鳴り響く夜に
In the night where the bell rings out.
迎えに行くから
I'm coming to get you.
同じビートで一つのナンバー
One number with the same beat.
奏でよう
Let's perform.
はーい！ということで、Candy-Go-Roundでしたー！
Hi! And that was Candy-Go-Round!
イエーイ！ありがとー！
Yay! Thank you!
見てー！すげー！
Look! Amazing!
すげーでっけー！
It's so huge!
ちょっとね、すごい大きい会場なんですけど、
It's a really big venue,
あらためてちょっと自己紹介していきましょうか。
but let's do our self-introductions properly.
はーい！じゃあまつりから行きますよ。みんなペンライトをまつり色に染めてくれ！
Yes! Then Matsuri will go first. Everyone, turn your penlights to Matsuri's color!
おー！
Oh!
それでは行きます。
Here I go.
みんなー、こんばんわっしょーい！
Everyone, good evening-wasshoi!
わっしょーい！
Wasshoi!
どうも、ホロライブの清楚担当、みんなのアイドル夏色まつりです！
Hello, I'm the pure one in charge of Hololive, everyone's idol, Natsuiro Matsuri!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ということでね、まつり先輩、どうですかこの景色？
So, Matsuri-senpai, how do you like this view?
いやもうすごい！もう、何？もう分からん、この規模が。
No, it's just amazing! Like, what? I don't even know, this scale.
分からん、じゃあ規模が分かんないよ。
I don't know, I just can't grasp the scale.
分かる。じゃあそれをね、ねねちにも体感してもらいましょう。自己紹介どうぞ！
I get it. Well, let's have Nenechi experience that too. Self-introduction, please!
やったー！みんなねねの色にしてねー！
Yay! Everyone, turn to Nene's color!
みんなー、こんねねー！
Everyone, Kon-Nene!
こんねねー！
Kon-Nene!
ホロライブ5期生、オレンジ担当アイドルVTuberの桃鈴ねねです！
Hololive 5th generation, the orange-colored idol VTuber, Momosuzu Nene!
イエーイ！
Yay!
すっご！
Wow!
すごすぎー！ねー！
It's too amazing! Right?
感想すごすぎー！やばい、語彙力がなくなりますよ。
That's an amazing reaction! Gosh, we're losing our vocabulary.
確かに。広いからね！
True. It's so vast!
それでは最後は、大空スバル！
And finally, Oozora Subaru!
ペンライト変えてください！
Please change your penlights!
いくよ！
Here I go!
ちわーす！ホロライブ2期生、大空スバルです！よろしくお願いします！
G'day! Hololive 2nd generation, Oozora Subaru! Nice to meet you!
イエーイ！
Yay!
いや、やば！すごいね！もうよく分からん、本当に実感がわかない、まだ。
Man, this is crazy! Amazing! I still can't quite wrap my head around it, for real.
ちょっとせっかく、だからさ、あのさ、ペンライトとさ、あのブロック分けしてさ、振るやつやろうよ！
Since we're here, let's do that thing where we divide the blocks and wave the penlights!
やろうやろう！
Let's do it!
じゃあ、スバルこっち担当。
Okay, Subaru will take this side.
じゃあまつり真ん中ね。
Then Matsuri will take the center.
行くよ！
Ready!
じゃあまずは、スバル側のひと、振ってー！
First, everyone on Subaru's side, wave!
おおー！すごい！ちょっとまだこっちの人振らないで、やめて！だめだよだめだよ！
Ooh! Amazing! Wait, people on this side, don't wave yet! Stop! Don't do it!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
じゃあ続いては、まつり先輩！
Next is Matsuri-senpai!
はい！じゃあ真ん中の人たち、行くよ！
Yes! Now, people in the center, here we go!
振れー！
Wave!
おおー！めっちゃ綺麗じゃん！
Ooh! It's so beautiful!
はい！じゃあ最後は、ねねち側のひと！
Yes! And finally, the people on Nenechi's side!
一番端の...
The ones on the far edge...
ペンライト振ってくれよな、みんな振ってー！
Wave your penlights, everyone wave them!
みんな！振ってー！
Everyone! Wave them!
さすがだ、みんな根っこ！
As expected, everyone's a Nekko!
泣いてた？
Were you crying?
それでは最後は全体で振りましょう。いくよ！
Now, let's all wave together for the last time. Here we go!
せーの！うわああああ！
One, two! Uwaaaaa!
すげー！これやってみたかったんだよ、スバルー！
Whoa! Amazing! I've always wanted to do this, Subaru!
本当すげー！ありがとう！
Really amazing! Thank you!
じゃあ、ちょっと真ん中戻りますか。
Now, shall we head back to the center?
戻りましょう、戻りましょう。
Let's go back, let's go back.
はい、ということでね、『Candy-Go-Round』披露させていただいたんですけど、
So, we just performed 'Candy-Go-Round',
どうでしたちょっと踊ってみて、まつり先輩？
but how was it for you to dance it, Matsuri-senpai?
いやね、めちゃめちゃ楽しかったね。あのね、最初は...
Well, it was super fun. You know, at first...
最初レッスンの時ね、もう、ここから入ったんですけど...
during the first lesson, I started from right here...
これな！マジで！
That's right! For real!
おっとおっとおっとって思ったんだけど、
I was like 'whoa, whoa, whoa',
まあ、意外にやってみると、まあ、できちゃうかな。
but well, once I actually tried it, I guess I could do it.
俺、上手だったよ、まつり先輩！
You were great, Matsuri-senpai!
すげー！上手だった！
Amazing! You were great!
ありがとう... 嬉しいな。ガチで照れてる。
Thank you... I'm happy. I'm actually blushing.
はい、じゃあ続いてねねち、どうでした踊ってみて？
Alright, next up, Nenechi, how was it for you to dance it?
いや、ねねはね、あのね、途中で真ん中に行くじゃんか。はいはい。
Well, as for Nene, you know, I go to the center in the middle. Right, right.
あの時のね、あの両端からのプレッシャー？ あれ、本当半端ない！
The pressure from both sides at that time? That was seriously intense!
やっときました！やっときました！
We gave it to her! We gave it to her!
やってみようよ！
Let's try it!
もういいよ！
That's enough already!
わ、すげー圧！ 先輩に挟まれし... こうしてね、みんなで... こうして...
Whoa, so much pressure! Being sandwiched by seniors... like this, everyone...
ぶつからないか心配でした。真ん中やっぱ目立っちゃうから。
I was worried we'd bump into each other. Since the center stands out, after all.
確かにな！ ミスできないプレッシャー。
True! The pressure of not being able to make a mistake.
でも、すごく良かったと思うよ！
But I think you were great!
そうなの、ごまかした、ごまかした。
That's right, I faked it, I faked it.
ごまかしたとか言うなお前！
Don't say you faked it!
そうだよ、ごまかしたんじゃないよ。根っこにも聞いてみな！
Exactly, you didn't fake it. Ask the Nekko too!
ねねちゃんは生きてるだけで凄いんだよ！
Nene-chan is amazing just for being alive!
そっち来ない！ 会場に聞けや！
Don't go that way! Ask the audience!
え、みんなどうだった？
Eh, how was it, everyone?
本当にね、やっぱダンス上手な三人って言って運営さんにね、集められたからね。
Yes, really, we were gathered by the management as the three good dancers, after all.
ねねち、そりゃ完璧だよね。
So Nenechi, of course you were perfect.
うん、そうよ！
Yeah, that's right!
あんまり、あの、いびらないで頂いて。
Please don't, uh, act so bossy.
泣かないで！ できてたよ！ すごく上手だった！
Don't cry! You did it! You were very good!
めちゃめちゃ可愛かった！ いいよ！ ありがとう！
You were super cute! It's okay! Thank you!
ということでですね、スバルたちの前にもね、かなたさんと、あとポルカちゃんと、
And so, before us, Kanata-san, Polka-chan,
あとね、クロヱがそれぞれね、個性的な世界観で... もうめっちゃみんなキャラ濃かったから。
and Chloe also showed their unique worlds... everyone's characters were so strong.
までもね、ここからはスバルたちも頑張っていきましょうと。
Well, but from here on, let's also do our best.
負けてられませんよ！
We can't let them beat us!
ということでですね、なんとですね、YouTubeのチラ見せがここまでなんですよ！
And so, believe it or not, the YouTube preview ends here!
あーよ、あーよ！ やっほやっほ！
A-yo, a-yo! Yahho yahho!
やっほやっほじゃない！ 今？
It's not 'Yahho yahho'! Now?
あともこれからも見たいよね？ むしろね、見たい気持ちが高まってると思うのよ、皆さん！
I'm sure you want to keep watching, right? I think everyone's desire to watch has only increased!
はい！ そんな人はね、概要欄をチェックして！
Yes! For those people, check the description box!
チェックら！ チェケラ！ ここからチケット買ってください！ お願いします！
Check it out! Please buy tickets from there! Please!
はい、ということでね、そろそろ時間なのでまつり先輩締めて頂いていいですか？
Alright, it's about time, so Matsuri-senpai, could you wrap things up?
時間が来ちゃったということで、次の曲に行きましょうか！
Since time is up, shall we move on to the next song!
それでは行きますよ！ せーの！ つながるホロライブー！
Here we go! One, two! Connecting hololive!
DAY1無料パートは終了いたしました
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The Day 1 free part has ended.
Thank you for watching!
DAY1無料パートは終了いたしました
The Day 1 free viewing period has ended.
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!
DAY1無料パートは終了いたしました
The DAY 1 free part has ended.
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!